techfeb.com 2013-05-05

# Privacy Policy of TechFeb

****TechFeb.com**** from time to time collect name, email address and/or details of website visitors. This may include the content of the mailing lists, any blog comments entered or any content in any other section. These details will not be passed onto any other third party or other organization unless we are required to by government or other law enforcement authority.

If you contribute content, such as discussion comments, to the site, your contribution may be publicly displayed including personally identifiable information.

**TechFeb.com** links to independently run websites outside of the **TechFeb.com** domain. We take no responsibility for the privacy practices or content of such web sites.

**TechFeb.com** uses cookies to save login details and visitors preferences, and to collect statistical information about the numbers of visitors to the site. To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.  For further information, consult the privacy policies of: www.google.com/privacypolicy.html

**TechFeb.com** is suitable for all ages, but we not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.

Comments are welcome. However, tasteless and insulting comments may be deleted. Any personal remarks and attacks may be deleted. The same holds true for off-topic comments. Any comments that reek of link spam or marketing messages will be deleted. **TechFeb.com** is not responsible for the content in comments other than those made by the blog author.

**Techfeb.com** would use the email address given by the user while commenting on the blog or while signing up, to send periodic email updates. The users can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the end of the newsletter emails or by using the [contact us](http://www.techfeb.com/contact-us/) form.

This policy will be updated from time to time. If we make significant changes to this policy after that time a notice will be posted on the main pages of the website. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

If you feel that **TechFeb.com** is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us using the [contact us](http://www.techfeb.com/contact-us/) form.

Our postal address is:  
_Sandeep Yadav for **TechFeb.com**_  
_Shanti Nager, Street No. 4,_  
_Bhiwani-127021, Haryana,_  
_INDIA_

### Advertisement Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **techfeb.com _[at]gmail.com_**.

At [www.techfeb.com](http://www.techfeb.com/) , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [www.techfeb.com](http://www.techfeb.com/) and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, [www.techfeb.com](http://www.techfeb.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

[www.techfeb.com](http://www.techfeb.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [www.techfeb.com](http://www.techfeb.com/)

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [www.techfeb.com](http://www.techfeb.com/) and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Technorati Media

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.techfeb.com](http://www.techfeb.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[www.techfeb.com](http://www.techfeb.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.techfeb.com](http://www.techfeb.com/)‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you feel that **TechFeb.com** is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us using the  [contact us](http://www.techfeb.com/contact-us/) form.

_Sandeep Yadav for **TechFeb.com**_  
_Shanti Nager, Street No. 4,_  
_Bhiwani-127021, Haryana,_  
_INDIA_  
Date:23-05-2011
